TURAN ADA

Phone number: +90(538)899-53-61
Date/place of birth=20.07.1997/Manisa
Gmail:turanada4597@gmail.com

I have graduated from Cukurova University as an electrical and electronics engineer. I developed my soft and hard skills through seminars, courses, students exchange programs and students clubs in my formal education life.

I had the opportunity to understand the basics of automation system by doing my internship at the control department of most important power plant of the Manisa industry I also gained valuable work experience, new skills and connections, as well as industry experience and confidence by doing internship in a company that undertakes electrical contracting works of most of factories in Manisa. So I have excellent interpersonal relations and wide technical skills.

I also had a chance to work as an electronic engineer in Hat Elektronik company. In May 2023, I was elected as the company's quality control manager and at the same time as the quality control representative. I organized the procedures for the organization and effective use of the quality management system. I made the definitions of the processes made during production more clear and understandable.

Now I have been working at Murat Ticaret as a project engineer. Murat Ticaret is Volex company which assembly wiring harnesses for automative sector. I have been providing the new product commissioning process for our customer AGCO_USA according to our customer's requirements

EXPERIENCES

07.11.2023-(STILL WORKING)

PROJECT ENGINEER, MURAT TICARET/VOLEX, BURSA

27.02.2023-23.08.2023

ELECTRONIC ENGINEER, HAT ELEKTRONIK, MANISA

07.2019 - 08.2019

INTERN, TEKNIKELLER MUHENDISLIK, MANISA

08.2018 - 09.2018

INTERN, MOSB POWER PLANT, MANISA

EDUCATION

02.2021 CUKUROVA UNIVERSITY ADANA

BACHELOR'S DEGREE, ELECTRICAL AND ELECTRONICS ENGINEERING(ENGLISH)

06.2015

HIGHSCHOOL, MANISA ANADOLU OGRETMEN LISESI MANISA

LANGUAGES

English	 	
Spanish		
German		

MILITARY SERVICE

• Completed in July 2023.

SOFT AND HARD SKILLS

- Leadership Skills
- Communication Skills
- Ability to work in a team
- Fast Learner
- Problem solving orientation

- C++/C#
- AutoCAD
- Python
- PowerBI
- MS Office
- Adobe Lightroom

CERTIFICATES

- TS-EN-ISO 9001
- TS-EN ISO 14001
- TS-EN ISO 22000
- Total quality management
- IATF 16949
- TS-EN ISO 19011
- SPC-MSA-FMEA-AIAG-APQP-8D
- 6 Sigma-5S
- Time management
- Body Language
- Problem solving techniques
- Comminucation skills
- Anger control and stress management
- C# Object Oriented programming
- Leadership in the 21'st century
 You can have a look my certificates in detail by using this link https://github.com/TuranAda/Certificates

SOCIAL EXPERIENCES

- Supervisor of Photography Club (ÇÜFOK), ADANA (2019-2020)
- Comenius F.I.V.E Project ,Constanta (2013)